When anyone is under the Mahadasha of Moon,
what kind of results does he get, what
experiences do he have, and what
kind of events can happen to us in this Dasha,
we will talk about this in today's video and we will
also talk about if this Dasha is
not going that well for you, then what kind of
measures should you take to make this Dasha smooth
and to comfortably spend this 10 year period of the
Dasha of Moon.
Welcome you and my name is
Adhyaksha, so let's talk
about the Mahadasha of Moon and when we are talking about the Mahadasha
of Moon, then this is the Mahadasha which
comes under Vimkshri Dashas, ​​so there are many types of
Dashas in the horoscope, the
most popular one among them is
and whenever any Pandit says that the Dasha of your Rahu,
Ketu or any planet is going on, then
generally only the Chaudhary Dasha is being referred to, there are
other Dashas also in the horoscope like
Charmandu Yogini, but here we are talking about
an important result under the Dasha of Moon
You will get that you will have a great eagerness
from within to change your house
and you will
try to live in the house you are living in
and you will try, that means you will
execute it for maximum time and change your house, so the
place of your house, the living
space where you live, is
quite probable to change under the condition of the Moon
and it will happen which will be
gathered from your current stay, but if the
Moon is not in a very well place then a
very heavy loan can be involved in it and later
you will be evicted from the same house,
living in that house also gives such a result under the condition of the Moon,
if the Moon is
not in welfare then it is possible that you want to stay in your house, want to
live with your parents and you have to leave your house due to compulsion, then if
your Moon is in a play place then you will get such a result, if it is a
good placement then you will go to a very
good house where there will be a big open and
big united environment where you will like to
live, you can be happy in such a house,
this is a very important result of this Mahadasha under the condition of the Moon.  If the
result is important,
what is the Moon anyway? It is a planet
that reflects sunlight.
And if you look at it, it is interesting that the Moon has
two aspects: one that appears light to us
and the other that remains dark. Similarly,
your personality changes under the Moon's condition.
Your personality will change such that
from the outside, you will appear very cheerful and very enthusiast to people.
Something may keep bothering you from within for the entire 10
years. If the Moon
is very well placed, suppose due to some good planning,
its position is with Jupiter or Venus, then
it will be slightly suppressed in the dark side
and it is possible that
you may not get bad results. But if the
Moon forms a conjunction with Rahu, Ketu, or any other sinful planet, then this
doubt within you will always remain within you
and will not even be revealed. You will always be
very cheerful and a very dynamic
personality to people, and people are
also attracted by your personality.
An attractive personality of yours will emerge under the Moon's condition.
In this Dasham, if you
are into mimicry or poetry, then
your skills will be enhanced in this Dasha and
you can establish a very good career in poetry, mimicry, imagination or creative
things.
It also depends on your future as to
what kind of change will come in your behavior under the Dasha of Moon.
Moon is a fickle planet and if you are in your
childhood during the Dasha of Moon,
then you will have a very fickle
personality. Even if you are a little older person,
you are in your 40s or 50s, then also
you will have a very
playful and full personality compared to the people in front of you and you will
also be known for that. So,
under the Dasha of Moon, your personality is very attractive.
People are attracted to you,
especially if you are ladies, they will be
more attracted to you, whether you yourself
are male or female, but ladies
will be attracted to you, there your more attractive
personality emerges.
And if you have seen the video till here, then
your Dasha of Moon is going on.  Or if
you have a great interest in this topic and
you liked the content of the video, then
please like it. This like is
my encouragement and
helps me make it golden. If you are new to the channel, then
subscribe to it so that you don't miss the other videos. You will be recommended
my videos and press the bell icon so that
you don't miss any notifications. The
10-year condition of the Moon
comes after the 6-year condition of the Sun.
In the condition of the Sun, if the Sun is in a good place, then
you reach very good heights
and in the Moon, you take the same thing
forward in a format of stability.
Now you try to stabilize things. The
Moon itself is
not a very stable planet. It has its own 27
phases. It decreases for 15 days and then decreases for 15 days. There are
different phases from Amavasya to Purnima. So, your mind
reduces its time because you
want it to be stable. There will
always be turmoil in your mind. For stability, there may be something
that is needed in your
life.  There is a problem again that we are
talking about that there will be a dark side, there will be some
worry that will always trouble you, so
in the condition of the Moon, you will always have
a negative thought inside you, things change
in the condition of the Moon
because see, the Moon does not have any light of its own,
it reflects the light of others, that is, it
reflects the light of the Sun, so
in the condition of the Moon, you are
also very much influenced by the people around you, you will be very much
influenced by their words and
take important decisions from them too,
in the condition of the Moon, you can get stomach-related diseases
and stomach infection or such
diseases which spoil the stomach or digestion
and the original is the factor of the mind, depression
also plays a very important
role, the Moon process is a direct
link, so now you can also become a victim of depression,
if the Moon is not in the right place, then
whatever is the placement of the Moon in your horoscope, it shows
what kind of results the Moon will give, if the
results of the place where your Moon is the owner,
there in that area also your mind will always be
worried that I have to do something or the other in that area.  If you want to
improve or
you are troubled by a person related to that area, then
in the condition of the Moon, you always keep
thinking about something or the other, where he
is the owner, so wherever the
placement of the Moon is, in that particular house
in your chart,
you start getting the results of that place immediately,
if the Moon is 4000 then it is almost certain that you will become a good stone
and you will
move into that house, you will get a new house under the condition of the Moon
which will be very beautiful, now the
question arises that if the decade of your Moon is
not going so well, then how
can you overcome it, in what
way can you pay off the results of the Moon
and spend it comfortably, can you bring
down its negative results, so the
most important thing you have to do is to offer water on the Shivling, as early as
you can in the morning, offer water on the Shivling, the more
you
offer water on the Shivling, the more your
Moon will be balanced, it is believed that the Moon is on the forehead of Lord Shiva, the more
you offer water to the Shivling, the more
your Moon will be balanced.  Only money will
come and that much energy will come in it. Secondly, if
your Moon is weak, if you were born
around Amavasya, in your horoscope the
Moon is very bright, it is
surrounded by negative energy and its own energy is not
emerging, then you should
visit the full moon when the Moon is
more than half in the sky, take important decisions, otherwise you should
not take important decisions,
if you cannot offer water on Monday,
visit the temple of Lord Gauri Shankar on Monday, so
wherever the Moon is weak, you should visit Lord Shiva,
pray to Lord Shiva, you will
get your results, you
can also wear a pearl after consulting an astrologer in your horoscope, so the pearl
is the ownership of the Moon, so you
can also wear a pearl, but definitely
consult someone first and then wear it only after that, so
this was my analysis, it will
bring water on the condition of the Moon, till then,
hello to you with a new topic related to astrology.